GPS追蹤警報
華盛頓特區
看看  腰果
Look at that, Cashew.
有人不聽話了喲
Someone's being a bad boy.
新約聖經  以弗所書  第四章
"並且不要叫神的聖靈憂愁
"Do not grieve the Holy Spirit of God,
你們原是受了他的印記  等候得贖的日子來到
by whom you were sealed for the day of redemption.
一切苦毒  惱恨  忿怒  喧嚷  毀謗
Let all bitterness and wrath and anger and clamour,
同一切的惡毒  都要從你們中間除掉
and evil speaking be put away from you with all malice.
你們要以恩慈相待
And be kind to one another,
心存慈憐
tenderhearted,
彼此饒恕"
forgiving one another."
還要我繼續讀嗎  還是換一本
Do you want me to keep going with this, or something else?
我無所謂
Doesn't matter to me.
我只是喜歡聽你讀
I just like hearing you read it.
道格  我要跟你說件事
Doug, there's something I need to talk to you about.
你說她只待幾個晚上
You said that she was just staying for a few nights.
她室友把她趕出來了  她沒地方可以去
Her roommate kicked her out. She doesn't have anywhere else to go.
不是我們的問題
Not our problem.
我總不能把她扔到大街上
I can't put her out on the street.
她叫什麼
What's her name?
-麗薩    -姓什麼
- Lisa.   - Lisa what?
你沒什麼好擔心的
You don't have anything to worry about.
她現在在哪裡
Where is she now?
在友誼會
At the fellowship.
和託兒所的一些小孩一起過夜
There's a sleepover with some of the kids from the day care.
她知道我嗎
Does she know about me?
不  我什麼都沒告訴她
No, I haven't told her anything.
我給了你空間
I have given you space.
我信任你  瑞秋
I trusted you, Rachel,
-你卻利用...    -我不會把她趕出去的
- and you've taken advantage--   - I'm not kicking her out.
弗·安德伍德  速來白宮  中國出現危機
我本可以什麼都不說  但我告訴了你
I could have said nothing, but I told you.
我得走了
I have to go.
下次我們再說話前  她最好走人
She better be gone by the next time we talk.
先生
Sir.
怎麼這麼久才來
What took you so long?
我五分鐘內就能整理好基本情況
I can have a briefing ready in five minutes.
不用了  我讓賽斯去做了
Don't bother. I had Seth do it.
他沒有安全許可
He doesn't have security clearance.
現在有了
Well, he does now.
總統先生  你先
Mr. President, after you.
在我辦公室等我
I'll see you in my office.
日本主權是最重要的
Japanese sovereignty is a matter of precedent.
首相先生  我的憂慮越來越深了
Mr. Prime Minister, my concern is escalation.
隸屬美國太平洋司令部的太平洋艦隊  司令部設在日本的橫須賀港
我只需要第七艦隊的一小部分
Well, I'm asking for a small portion of the 7th Fleet.
我們必須讓中國認清局面
We must bring China into line.
向中國展示  日美聯盟堅不可破
Show them that the U.S. and Japan maintain a strong alliance.
你直接和北京方面聯繫過嗎
Have you reached out directly to Beijing?
他們拒不承認該島屬於日本
No recognition that the island belongs to Japan.
我得和我的團隊討論一下  擬訂一個計劃
Well, I'd like to speak to my team and formulate a plan.
謝謝  總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
謝謝  首相先生
Thank you, Mr. Prime Minister.
上將  給後入會的解釋一下
Admiral, for those catching up...
大概六小時前  兩艘中國驅逐艦進入了
Two Chinese destroyers entered waters
與那國島附近方圓三英里的水域
within three miles of Yonaguni Island here,
也就是這裡
approximately six hours ago.
可以看到該島離臺灣很近
See how close the island is to Taiwan.
這與釣魚島的僵局性質不同
This is different than the standoff over the Senkaku Islands.
可能是為航線的事
It could have to do with shipping routes.
或者貿易戰  柿子總是撿軟的捏
Or the trade war. They can't pick on the big kids,
所以他們對實力較弱的下手
so they're picking on the little one.
-看到了嗎    -什麼
- Do you see that?   - What?
小巷裡  二號機
In the alley, camera two.
全體注意  白人男子
All posts, white male,
帽衫  帆布袋
hooded sweatshirt, duffel bag.
法爾大街東南側
Southeast side of Fair St.
放下包
Put down the bag.
放下包  把手放在頭上
Put down the bag and place your hands on your head.
站住別動
Stay right where you are.
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood?
可以請你下樓來嗎
Will you come downstairs, please?
弗蘭西斯在哪
Where's Francis?
他在白宮耽擱了  有個緊急會議
He got delayed at the White House, there was an emergency meeting.
出什麼事了
What's going on?
我會在安全屋做解釋
I'll explain in the safe room.
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用於任何商業盈利行為
翻譯 某豚   香茗小焙   葉某人
翻譯 小飯   癢癢   衛老哥
藍光版調整  timhal@HDWinG字幕組   後期 餓得慌
顧問 老杜   校對 草草   總監 草草
本字幕由YYETS翻譯 HDWinG字幕組修正 請勿去掉製作者資訊
《紙牌屋》
第二季  第十集
第七艦隊在關島附近嗎
The 7th Fleet is near Guam?
北面90英里
Ninety miles north.
一週內就能派艦只去與那國島
We could have ships to Yonaguni in less than a week.
但僅僅向是那個方向行進
But even sending them in that direction
都會被中國衛星發現
will be picked up by the Chinese satellites.
我們必須和盟友保持統一戰線  這毋庸置疑
Well, we have to stand with our allies, that can't be in question.
如果我們不派遣艦隻  而是發表聲明
What if we don't send ships, just make a strong statement
強烈譴責中國擅入日本領海
condemning their excursion into Japan's territorial waters.
我們得給中國足夠的壓力
We still have to offer the Chinese an incentive
讓他們召回驅逐艦
to call back their destroyers.
不論採取什麼措施
Whatever overtures we make,
要做好應變計劃
I'd like to have contingency plans in place.
已經在起草  先生
Already drafting them, sir.
凱茜  通過外交途徑聯繫北京方面
Cathy, open up a diplomatic channel with Beijing.
看看是否有具體要求
See if there's a concrete ask,
如果沒有  就提供一些選擇
if they don't have one, let's create a list of options.
這就去辦  先生
Right away, sir.
同日本海軍的協調如何了
How about coordination with the Japanese navy?
去吧  暫時不要把我方海軍牽扯進去
Go. Don't engage with our navy yet.
我要直接和御城首相對話
I want to talk directly to Prime Minister Oshiro
表達我們的意思
and express our intentions.
前海軍陸戰隊員
Former marine.
他出現在警戒線附近  拿著一個
He showed up at the outer perimeter with explosives
裝滿爆炸物的包  身上也綁著炸藥
in a duffel bag and strapped to his body.
天吶
Jesus.
我們逮捕了他  媒體沒得到風聲
We apprehended him. The press isn't aware.
很好  別走漏風聲
Well, let's keep it that way.
他宣稱對寄去國會大廈的
He claimed he was responsible for sending
裝有白色粉末的郵件負責
the package of white powder to the Capitol.
那麼這回他打算對我動真格的
So this time he really wanted to take me out for real.
不能算是
Not exactly.
他妻子上週揹著他墮胎了
His wife got an abortion last week without telling him.
天吶  是針對我
Oh, my god. It was me.
對  你是目標
Yes, you were the target.
請你和我們留在樓下  安德伍德夫人
We'd like to keep you down here with us, Mrs. Underwood,
直到我們確定他是單獨行動
until we can confirm he was acting alone.
我留下陪你
I'll stay.
不  你得回白宮去
No. You have to get back to the White House.
我可以在家辦公
I can work from here.
弗蘭西斯  我沒事  真的
Francis, I'm fine. Honestly.
我就待在這兒
I'm just gonna be in here.
你要時刻陪著她
I want you to stick with her at all times.
有任何事都通知我
Keep me informed of everything.
他馬上就下班了  先生
He's almost done with his shift, sir.
我可以安排別的探員
I can put another agent on--
不  我就要密查姆
No, I want it to be Meechum.
一定  先生
Absolutely, sir.
需要我待多久我就待多久
As long as necessary.
我儘快回來
I'll be back as soon as I can.
沒事的
It's OK.
別去加州
Don't go to California.
我還想連任呢
Be nice to be reelected.
你會贏的
You're gonna win.
如果我不在選民前露面就不會
Not if I don't give the voters more face time.
你什麼時候紋的
When did you get it?
在軍隊的時候
The Army?
是
Yeah.
那之後又添了些
It's grown since then.
和我說說
Tell me about it.
不
No.
為什麼不
Why not?
我不想說
I don't want to.
你在幹什麼
What are you doing?
和我說說這個紋身
Tell me about the tattoo.
這不公平
That's not fair.
那又怎麼樣
So what?
你覺得讓我溼了我就什麼都會說嗎
You think you can just get me wet and I'll spill everything?
我不是覺得
I don't think so...
我知道你會
...I know so.
告訴我
Tell me.
我喜歡那種疼痛
I like the pain.
針扎的疼
Of the needle?
對
Yeah.
有多疼
How bad did it hurt?
非常疼
It hurt a lot.
你喜歡疼痛
You like when it hurts?
我殺過很多人
I killed a lot of people.
什麼
What?
在軍隊的時候
In the Army.
疼痛
The pain...
對我有幫助
...it helped.
繼續
Finish.
我只能找到他開第一家工廠時
The most I could find was some wrangling with the EPA
和環保局的一些爭端
when he opened his first plant,
但那都是40年前了
but that was almost 40 years ago.
我們需要更多
We need more.
我要塔斯克消失
I want Tusk gone.
我和道爾會繼續查的
Doyle and I will keep looking.
你到現在還什麼都沒找到
If you haven't found anything now,
你怎麼知道你能找到
what makes you think you will?
或許我們忽略了什麼
Maybe we missed something.
我覺得沒有  但可以再試試
I doubt it, but we could try.
你以為塔斯克此刻不是在謀劃下一波進攻嗎
You think Tusk isn't planning his next attack even as we speak?
我們查得很徹底  先生
We've been thorough, sir.
他從來不留痕跡
He doesn't leave footprints.
要改變策略嗎
You want to shift tactics?
那賭場  我們儘快曝光
The casino. We go public as soon as possible.
你說那是萬不得已的辦法
You said that was a last resort.
賽斯  想個辦法
Seth, you need to find a way
曝光賭場  又不會扯上我們
to make that happen so it doesn't link back to us.
如果我們點了這把火
If we launch that missile,
可能會燒到我們自己
it could blow us up too.
如果我們控制好就不會
Not if we spin it right.
-如果我們集中在...    -賽斯
- If we keep the focus on--   - Seth.
你是來聽的  不是來出謀劃策的
You're here to listen, not contribute.
我要是不想他出謀劃策就不會讓他來
I wouldn't have him here if I didn't want him to contribute.
先生  他接手才三小時
Sir... he's been sitting with this for three hours.
我已經研究了三個月
I've been working on it for three months.
而什麼都沒實現
And accomplished nothing.
我們該進攻了
It's time we go on the offensive.
你有什麼辦法
What do you think?
艾拉·薩伊德
Ayla Sayyad.
她已經在查塔斯克和馮了
She's already digging into Tusk and Feng.
她知道多少
How close is she?
她從沒提過賭場
She never mentioned a casino,
但現在我知道要害在哪
but now that I know what the dots are,
我可以讓她把一切聯繫起來
I can see that she's starting to connect them.
五角大樓還沒有發言
The Pentagon isn't talking yet.
我猜他們在等白宮
I imagine they're waiting on the White House.
我聽說從昨晚起他們就在
I hear there have been regular meetings
戰況室頻繁開會
in the Situation Room since last night.
我過會兒打給你
Let me call you right back.
-你好    -你好琳恩  我是艾拉
- Hello?   - Hey, Lynne, it's Ayla.
我剛發給你張照片
I just sent you a picture.
收到了
Yeah, I got it.
這是什麼意思
What does it mean?
有點奇怪
It's strange,
說不太通啊
it doesn't really make sense.
告訴我
Tell me.
字面翻譯應該是"追隨貨幣"
"Pursue currency" would be like the most literal translation.
或者"追隨金錢"
Or "pursue money."
跟蹤資金
Follow the money?
這麼說也行
That could work.
謝謝  琳恩
Thanks, Lynne.
我喜歡你的新佈置
I like what you've done.
沙發是新的嗎
This sofa, it's new?
還有這些燈
These lamps as well?
我做了些改動
I've made a few changes.
太熟悉一個地方
You get so used to a place,
再小的改變也會很顯眼
the smallest things stand out.
抱歉我沒能更快答覆你
I apologize for not being responsive sooner.
我最近都在忙中期選舉
I've been focused on the midterms.
你不用向我解釋
Oh, there's no need to explain.
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood,
你知道我多麼尊敬你的初衷
you know how much I respect your intentions,
但我經過深思熟慮  還是認為
but I've thought deeply about this and
我不能聯署現在這份法案
I can't cosponsor the bill in its current form.
民事監管的提議太過極端
Civilian oversight is too extreme a step,
不過我願意重新考慮
but I'd be happy to revisit some of
不那麼極端的提議
the other less extreme proposals.
你認為我們太極端嗎
You think we're being extremist?
我也想在這件事上出力
I want to help with this issue,
但這份法案要經過...
but this bill goes through--
這份法案要通過三軍委員會
This bill is through Armed Services.
進入辯論指日可待
This bill has a date on the floor.
幾乎眾議院所有的女性
Almost every woman in the House
都支援這份法案
supports this bill.
而我不能成為其中之一
And I can't be one of them.
你騙了我們
So you lied to us.
我沒有
I didn't lie.
我沒有撒謊
我想幫你們
I want to help.
只要我們重新考慮部分措辭
As long as we rethink some of the language.
你是不是因為嘉樂威醜聞的事
Are you trying to distance yourself from us
刻意和我們保持距離
because of the Galloway scandal?
不是
No.
也許你認為和我合作
Maybe you think it hurts your chances
會對你謀求連任不利
of reelection if you associate with me.
不是因為這個
That's not it.
是因為我打心眼裡不贊同這種方式
It's because I honestly don't believe in this approach.
你意識到這會讓外人怎麼看嗎
Do you realize the message this sends?
你是國會兩黨唯一一位女性領導人
The only woman in congressional leadership in both parties,
而你選擇退出
and you bow out?
如果法案真能進入辯論
If the bill goes to the floor as is,
我不會單單退出
I won't just bow out.
我會積極反對
I'll actively fight it.
你從未問過我的立場
You never asked my position.
你只是假設
You assumed.
我真無法相信你會是什麼立場
I can't imagine what that position must be.
我曾在戰區服役
I've served in war zones,
我對這事的重要性有親身體會...
I know firsthand how important--
我們現在談的不是戰區
We're not talking about war zones.
而是性侵犯
We're talking about sexual assault.
如果讓特別軍事法庭
How about a military commission
審查內部機制呢
to review the internal mechanisms --
我們不需要更多研究  我們需要改革
We don't need more studies. We need reform.
等我從加利福尼亞回來以後
Well, let's continue this conversation
再繼續今天的對話吧
when I return from California.
我後天回來
I'll be back the day after tomorrow,
但願你會改變想法
if you change your mind.
我不會
I won't.
但我希望你會
But I hope you change yours.
中國認為我們覺得可以收買他們是種侮辱
China was insulted at the notion we could buy them off.
需要我再聯繫錢主席嗎
Well, do I need to call President Qian?
我看他不會與他的部長意見相左
I doubt he would contradict one of his ministers.
看看他是否願意一對一談
See if he's willing to talk one on one.
你得知道  先生
You should know, sir,
日本也正準備
Japan is also preparing
調遣三艘驅逐艦和一艘輕巡洋艦
to deploy three destroyers and a light cruiser.
他們在加大賭注
They're upping the ante.
讓海因斯大使聯絡日本首相
Have Ambassador Hines get in touch with the prime minister,
看日本能否暫時按兵不動
and ask if Japan will hold off
讓我先和北京取得聯繫
until I make contact with Beijing.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
你休息過嗎
Have you gotten any rest at all?
沒  你呢
No, have you?
還沒
Not yet.
克萊爾怎麼樣
How's Claire?
特勤局認為是孤立事件
Secret Service thinks it's an isolated attempt,
但他們加強了防備
but they're being cautious.
經過嘉樂威的事和電視採訪
After the Galloway thing and the interview,
半數國民當她是嬰兒殺手
half the country thinks she's a baby killer,
或出軌者  或兩者皆是
or an adulterer, or both.
但克萊爾挺坦然的
But Claire's taking it in stride.
我們沒事的
We're in good hands.
真是太可怕了
That's very frightening.
怪不得你無暇休息
I can see why you haven't slept.
我們有一人得休息會兒
One of us should,
還是做決策的那個休息吧
probably the one that's calling all the shots.
不用  我可以再堅持一會兒
No, I can hold out a little while longer.
別  回宅邸吧  去陪陪你妻子
No, go to the residence, spend some time with your wife.
回來後會感覺煥然新生
You'll come back feeling like a new man.
說真的
Honestly, it's...
這裡的壓力反而更小
less stressful here.
諮詢沒效果嗎
Counseling hasn't helped?
不是  慢慢在起效吧
No, it has... slowly.
琳達辭職的時候
I got rid of Christina
我也開除了克里斯蒂娜
when Linda resigned.
我聽說了
I heard.
情況多少改善了一些  但是...
It's improved things some, but...
還需要努力
...there's still work to do.
但是想想都讓我覺得累
Makes me tired just to think about it.
你應該不是第一位
Well, you probably wouldn't be the first president
在這幾個沙發上打盹的總統
to get a little shut-eye on one of these sofas.
我在開玩笑呢
I was joking.
我沒有
I wasn't.
行行好  休息一下吧
Do the free world a favor and get some rest.
我先出去了
I'll let you be.
不用  待在這兒吧
No, stick around.
如果錢主席
You should be nearby
打電話來  你也該在場
if President Qian wants to get on the phone.
我一向討厭睡眠的必要性
I've always loathed the necessity of sleep.
它跟死亡一樣  能讓最強大的人倒下
Like death, it puts even the most powerful men on their backs.
特區豪車巴士租賃
DC Limo and Bus Rental.
這裡是阿道希賭場的出行部
I'm calling from the Adohi Casino's travel department.
我們有公司賬戶
We've got a corporate account.
我看看
Let's see...
抱歉  我們記錄裡沒有
Yeah, I'm sorry, we don't have one in our records.
我的錯  我一定是打錯電話了  謝謝
My mistake. I must have called the wrong limo service. Thank you.
密蘇里巴士豪車
Missouri Bus and Limo.
這裡是阿道希賭場的出行部
I'm calling from the Adohi Casino's travel department.
你不是達林
You're not Darlene.
不是  達林請病假了
No. Darlene is out sick.
由我代班  我叫帕姆
I'm filling in for her. My name is Pam.
我能為你做什麼  帕姆
How can I help you, Pam?
我們明天要接待來自中國的航班
We've got a flight coming in from China tomorrow.
我們需要車
We'll need some transportation.
有多少乘客
How many you got coming?
我手裡沒有乘客名單
I don't have the manifest right
照常嗎
The usual?
沒錯
That's right.
那就是一輛豪華巴士
So a luxury bus.
能坐多少人
How many does that fit?
55人
55.
通常拉20個人左右
Usually about 20 come in.
-空間應該足夠了    -太棒了  謝謝
- Should be plenty of room.   - That's great. Thanks.
你覺得她是真心不認同
Do you think it's really her conscience,
還是因為法案太有爭議
or because the bill is controversial?
如果她只是想避免爭議
I don't think she would have threatened to fight us
就不會說要積極反對了
if all she wanted to do was avoid controversy.
我去跟她談
I'll talk to her.
我真的很希望這個法案能通過
I really want this bill to pass.
我知道  我也是
I know you do, so do I.
我們現在非常需要傑姬  弗蘭西斯
We need Jackie more than ever, Francis.
我現在成壞女人了
I'm damaged goods,
就因為亞當那事
this whole Adam thing.
不  你不是
No, you're not.
我們一起挺過去了
We fought past that.
還是有很多人相信那確有其事
Well, there's plenty of people who still believe it's true.
我們會度過這一關的  我發誓
We'll get it passed, I promise.
不  謝謝
No, thanks.
得了
Come on.
我自己抽沒意思
It's no fun doing it alone.
我們可以去跑跑步
We could just go for a run.
死亡威脅平息前  不能再去跑步了
No more runs until the death threats die down,
這是新規則
that's the new rule.
但他們讓你去辦公室了
But they let you go to the office.
因為我坐的是防彈車
Because I was in a bulletproof car.
那這樣一來我們是沒戒菸了嗎
Does this mean we've officially not quit?
我們向來不會輕言放棄  不是嗎
We've never been quitters, have we?
先生  安德伍德夫人
Sir, Mrs. Underwood,
很抱歉打擾你們
sorry to interrupt.
我要回家了
I was gonna head home,
但如果你們想讓我留下  我就留下
but I'll stick around if you want me to.
不  你已經熬很久了  去睡會兒吧
Oh, no. You've been up long enough. Get some sleep.
我明天一早就回來
I'll be back first thing in the morning.
謝謝你今天照顧我
Thank you for looking after me today.
我的榮幸  女士
My pleasure, ma'am.
先生  安德伍德夫人  再見
Sir, Mrs. Underwood.
他非常盡忠
He's very dedicated.
確實
He is.
很難找到艾德華這樣的人
It's rare to find someone like Edward.
怎麼了
What?
你從沒直呼他名字
You never use his first name.
是嗎
Oh, did I?
我覺得這樣談論她不太好
I don't feel right talking about her like this.
就是...嚴格講  她現在是我上司
It's just... technically, she's my boss now.
有規矩的
There's a certain protocol.
這是道格下的命令
This is coming directly from Doug.
也就是說是副總統下的命令
Which means it's coming directly from the vice president.
我見到過幾次丹頓先生
I have seen Mr. Danton around from time to time.
你知道他跟議員女士在商討什麼嗎
Do you know what he and the congresswoman were discussing?
不知道  都是私人會面
No, they were private meetings.
你有預約日程表嗎
Do you have the appointment schedule?
我想看看日期
I'd like to look at the dates.
不是正式約會
These weren't formal appointments.
他就是順路來看看
He just stops by.
大多數都是晚上很晚的時候
Most of the time pretty late at night.
沃克
馮
塔斯克
安德伍德
拉尼根
錢是不是從中國來的
Did the money originate in China?
錢來自部落收入
The money came from tribal revenue.
我們的聯邦選舉委員會報告上寫得很清楚
As our FEC reports clearly stated.
我換個說法
Let me rephrase.
這些部落收入是否來自
Did any of that revenue come from
去你賭場的中國遊客
Chinese visitors who gambled at your casino?
我們有來自世界各地的遊客
We have visitors from all over the world.
我只關注
I'm speaking specifically
一個叫馮山德的商人
about a businessman named Xander Feng.
我不知道那是誰
I have no idea who that is.
我查到空管局的記錄顯示
I'm looking at FAA flight records that show
他名下的一架私人飛機
a private plane he owns
曾多次飛抵堪薩斯城
making numerous trips to Kansas City.
我問過密蘇里巴士豪車
And I spoke with Missouri Bus and Limo,
他們負責把中國遊客接到你的賭場
which has transported Chinese visitors to your casino.
賽義德女士
Ms. Said--
薩伊德
Sayyad.
薩伊德女士  我回你的電話
Ms. Sayyad, the only reason I returned your call
只是因為你在《電訊報》工作
was because you work for The Telegraph.
我不是每天都能接受
It's not every day that I get a call
你們這種大報的採訪
from a paper as big as yours.
但我不明白你究竟想問什麼
But I don't know what you're trying to get at here,
所以如果你不介意
so if you'll excuse--
那雷蒙德·塔斯克呢
What about Raymond Tusk?
他怎麼了
What about him?
馮和塔斯克有關係
Feng has ties to Tusk.
塔斯克與總統有關係
Tusk has ties to the president.
你與馮有關係
You have ties to Feng.
這看起來像是外國資金
That looks like foreign money
被用來左右政治...
being used to influence political--
你所暗示的事不僅錯誤
What you're insinuating is not only wrong,
而且是誹謗
it's libelous.
如果真實就不是
Not if it's true.
我會毫不猶豫地讓我的律師介入
I won't bat an eyelash getting my attorneys involved.
塔斯克也這麼威脅我
Tusk made the same threat.
如果一個身家四百億的人嚇不倒我
If a man worth $40 billion doesn't intimidate me,
你也嚇不倒我  拉...
you certainly don't, Mr. Lan--
喂
Hello?
他掛斷了
He hung up.
我和這完全沒關係  雷蒙德
I had nothing to do with it, Raymond.
我在電話這頭都聞得到謊言的臭氣
I can smell the horseshit through the phone.
你覺得我會冒這麼大的險嗎
You think I'd put myself at this great a risk?
兔子急了都咬人
Desperate men are capable of anything.
我和你一樣希望事情平息
I want it to go away just like you do.
那就讓她停手
Then pull her back.
我控制不了媒體  雷蒙德
I have no control over the press, Raymond.
你是搬起石頭砸自己的腳  不是我的  弗蘭克
You'll destroy yourself, Frank, not me.
多謝你多餘的忠告
Thank you for that unsolicited advice.
和道爾一起
Work with Doyle,
確保我們沒有弱點
make sure we have no weak spots.
我這就打電話給他
I'll call him now.
南茜怎麼說
What did Nancy say?
看來傑姬可能和敵人上床了
Well, it looks like Jackie may be sleeping with the enemy.
拉尼根說我們有誹謗的風險沒說錯
Lanagin is correct in saying we run the risk of libel.
他們之間的聯繫是有事實依據的
These links are supported by fact.
都是單線  你不能連成圈
Individually, but you can't complete the circle.
我不是說我們要大標題寫
I'm not saying the headline should read:
"洗錢黑幕揭祕"  加大驚歎號
Money Laundering Scheme Exposed! Exclamation point.
只是把我們已知的情況原樣呈現
Just that we present the landscape as we currently know it.
我們主要是一家財經報紙
We're first and foremost a financial paper.
很多讀者都崇拜雷蒙德·塔斯克
Many of our readers worship Raymond Tusk.
那我們就該保護他嗎
So we just protect him?
我們不能暗示我們無法證實的聯繫
We don't insinuate connections we can't back up.
有任何訴訟的機會
If there's any basis for litigation,
他的團隊肯定不會放過
you can be sure his team will be aggressive.
他們以前也曾讓報社破產
They've bankrupted papers before.
我覺得你應該慢慢來
I think you should slow down and take your time.
什麼時候你有了完整的故事
When, and if, you have a story--
馬克斯菲爾德先生
Mr. Maxfield,
雷蒙德·塔斯克打電話過來
Raymond Tusk is on the line.
你給他打電話了嗎
Did you put in a call to him?
昨天
Yesterday.
他指名要找你  先生
He's specifically asking for you, sir.
我們和拉尼根通話還不到半小時
We got off the phone with Lanagin less than 30 minutes ago.
說明拉尼根立刻打電話給塔斯克了
That means that Tusk was the first call Lanagin made.
告訴他我會打回去
Tell him I'll return.
你聯繫過白宮了嗎
Did you reach out to the White House?
他們在明天總統的新聞釋出會前
They're not talking to anyone until after the president
不接受任何採訪
does his press briefing tomorrow.
好吧
All right.
把事情再詳細給我說一遍
Walk me through all of this again, point by point.
華爾街電訊報  中國資金  阿道希賭場
沒有搜索到相關網頁
密查姆
Meechum.
我們明天再說  先生
We can talk tomorrow, sir.
不用  怎麼了
No. What is it?
我想申請全職做你妻子的安保人員
I'd like to put in a request to be on your wife's detail full-time.
直到死亡威脅消失
At least until the death threats quiet down.
這很體貼
That's very thoughtful.
你不同意我是不會去的  先生
I'll only do it if you approve, sir.
你和克萊爾談過了嗎
Have you spoken to Claire?
她回來的時候說過了  她覺得不錯
When she came home. She likes the idea.
那就這樣做吧
Then I think we should do it.
我去告訴洛克蘭探員
I'll let Agent Rockland know.
抱歉打擾  先生
Sorry for interrupting you, sir.
你沒打擾什麼
You didn't interrupt anything.
晚安  先生
Good night, sir.
晚安  密查姆
Good night, Meechum.
你肯定猜不到剛才發生了什麼
You'll never believe what just happened.
什麼
What?
密查姆走進辦公室
Meechum came into the office
發現我看的東西
and found me watching something...
不是新聞
...other than the news.
不是吧
Oh, no.
他很懂規矩
He was very professional about it.
-你有沒有...    -沒有  我只是看而已
- Were you...?   - No, no, no. I was just watching.
真是好笑
That's really funny.
你呢  你在看什麼
What about you? What are you watching?
康納給我的視訊
The video Connor gave me.
我們第一次競選州參議員
It's our first state senate race.
我都忘乾淨了
I forgot about that.
我也是  今早在桌上看到才想起來
So did I, until I found it in the desk this morning.
讓我看看
Let me see.
...經歷過  就像我
...been there, like I have.
當然  有點德州味兒無傷大雅
Of course, it doesn't hurt to have a little Texas in them...
-老天  我們當年多年輕    -是啊
- My God, look how young we are.   - I know.
大家都很和善  很熱情
Everyone here has been so kind, and so welcoming.
過不了多久她就要在克萊姆森紮根了
We'll have her rooting for Clemson before too long.
這我可做不到
That's where I have to draw the line.
你懷念和亞當在一起的日子嗎
Do you miss being with Adam?
你怎麼提起這個來
Where did that come from?
懷念嗎  不
Miss it? No.
你肯定偶爾會懷唸的
Well, you must, sometimes.
我有段時間很在乎他
He meant a lot to me for a while.
但都是過去了
But that's done now.
那你呢
What about you?
我什麼
What about me?
你覺得不滿足嗎
Are you unsatisfied?
我們現在要時時處處小心
There's just too much at stake now.
沒法信任任何人
No one we can trust.
失去了曾經的自由
We don't have the freedom we once did.
也許這樣更好
Maybe it's better this way.
不會分心
No room for distractions.
我不介意犧牲
I don't mind the sacrifice.
我們選擇了這個
We chose this instead.
有一件事我們可以達成一致  這兒的肋排更好吃
I think the one thing we can agree on is the ribs here are better.
他就是不把我惹火不罷休
See, he's just trying to get under my skin.
不  根本無可爭辯
No, it's not even debatable...
加州之行怎麼樣
How was California?
很累
Exhausting.
兩天裡12個活動
12 events in two days.
這是金門嗎
Is this the Golden Gate?
對
Yes.
我原來在那裡掛了幅未建成的國會大廈蝕刻板畫
I had an etching right there of the Capitol before it was finished.
花了85年才完工
Took 85 years to complete it.
這座橋建了多久
How long did it take to complete the bridge.
大概四年
Uh, about four years.
羅斯福第二次就職演說後不久通行
It opened a few months after FDR's second inaugural.
羅斯福是個能成事的人
That was a man who got things done.
信仰堅定  從不動搖
Strong beliefs. and he stuck to them.
但在必要時也會妥協
But compromised when he had to.
我猜你是來討論克萊爾的法案的
I assume you're here to talk about Claire's bill.
那可不是什麼鬧著玩的項目
It's not a pet project.
兩黨加起來有三四十個聯署人
There are three dozen cosponsors on either side of the aisle.
-這是個嚴肅的法案    -我不這麼認為
- It's a serious bill.   - I don't disagree.
措辭可能稍顯隨意
Except with the language.
我可以解釋我的看法
I can explain my thinking,
但恐怕不能說服你
but I doubt I'll convince you anymore--
先不提什麼軍隊尊嚴
Putting aside the military's honor,
軍階等級  等等一切你珍視的東西
chain of command, all the things that you hold dear...
就考慮一個簡單的事實
...let's consider one simple fact.
要不是我  你坐不進這間辦公室
You wouldn't have this office if it weren't for me.
我說得很清楚  我不會做傀儡
I made very clear that I wouldn't be a puppet.
我也不想控制你
I'm not trying to pull strings,
但你好歹表現出一點感激
but you could show a little gratitude.
別的都可以
If it were anything else,
副總統先生
Mr. Vice President...
但這件事不行
but not this.
這件事必然要成功  你至多只會讓好事多磨
All you're doing is making the inevitable more difficult.
並非一定會成功  克萊爾還沒得到足夠的支援
It's not inevitable. Claire doesn't have the votes yet.
你真想在這件事上和我們對著幹
You really want to fight us on this.
我一點不想和你對著幹
I don't want to fight you at all,
所以才向克萊爾建議  我們坐下來談談
which is why I suggested to Claire that we sit down--
我既沒有時間  也沒有興趣和你討價還價
I neither have the time nor the inclination to negotiate with you!
聯署法案
Cosponsor the bill,
拉好該死的票
whip the damn votes,
這不是請求
I'm no longer asking.
那我也不會再聽了
Then I'm no longer listening.
你該謝我的  可不止這間辦公室
You don't have just this office to thank me for.
你如果能連任  還要為那個謝我
If you win reelection, you can thank me for that, too.
那些攻擊廣告可不是平白無故消失的
Those attack ads didn't just disappear on their own.
你是什麼意思
What do you mean?
你去問問雷米·丹頓吧
Why don't you ask Remy Danton.
順便再問問他雷蒙德·塔斯克的事
And ask him about Raymond Tusk while you're at it.
這樣的枕邊對話會很有意思的
That ought to make for some very interesting pillow talk.
繼續好好工作  南茜
You keep up the good work, Nancy.
好的  副總統先生
I will, Mr. Vice President.
真懷念你在身邊的日子
I miss having you around,
但現在你是我的眼線
but you're my eyes and ears now,
否則我立馬把你要回來
otherwise I'd steal you back in a heartbeat.
謝謝  先生
Well, thank you, sir.
你這麼說  對我意義重大
It means a lot to me that you say that.
道格
Doug?
我忙著呢
I'm busy.
報道剛剛見報了
The story just broke.
他們算準了總統的新聞釋出會
They timed it with the president's press conference.
幫我轉接副總統
Connect me with the vice president.
政治行動委員會資金引起質疑  雷蒙德·塔斯克  中國資金  國會和白宮
第七艦隊目前部署在關島附近
So the 7th Fleet is currently positioned near Guam,
如果中國將船隻
where it will remain
從日本領海撤出  第七艦隊也會原地不動
if China removes its ships from Japan's sovereign waters.
我和御城首相保持著頻繁的溝通
I've been in frequent touch with prime minister Oshiro,
也親自向錢主席發出提議
and have made personal overtures to President Qian.
我對緩解緊張局勢持樂觀態度
And I remain optimistic that tensions will be quelled
危機不會進一步升級
without any further escalations.
現在我可以回答一些問題
So, with that, I'll take some questions.
亨利  你先來
Henry, you first.
你可以對《華爾街電訊報》的報道發表評論嗎
Can you comment on the Wall Street Telegraph article--
我來之前才剛知道這件事
I was just notified of that moments before I joined you.
我還沒來得及看呢  簡
I haven't had a chance to read it yet. Yeah, Jane?
總統先生
Mr. President,
你能給我們講一下你和雷蒙德·塔斯克的關係嗎
would you walk us through your history with Raymond Tusk?
我是來回答關於中日關係的問題的  馬克
I'm here to answer questions on Sino-Japanese relations. Mark?
報道中提到馮山德
The article mentions Xander Feng,
一位富有而有影響力的中國商人
a wealthy and influential Chinese businessman --
除非問題與我剛剛的聲明有關
Unless this has to do with the statement I just made...
的確有關  總統先生
It does, Mr. President.
馮和常委有聯繫
Feng has ties to the standing committee
而我們目前和中國陷入僵局
and we're currently in a standoff with the Chinese.
經濟上
Economically--
非常感謝各位
Thank you all very much.
我並不怕這故事的開端
It's not beginning the story that I fear,
我怕的是不知道結局將如何
it's not knowing how it will end.
現在人人都是靶子了
Everyone is fair game now,
我也是
including me.
這完全在意料之中
This is par for the course,
我們已經發現沃克總統就是如此
for what we've come to expect from President Walker.
印第安捐助者  沃克對詳情閃爍其辭
如果他想賣出一輛新車
Whenever he's selling a shiny new car,
他就滔滔不絕
he can't say enough about it.
引擎壞了
The engine breaks down,
變速器不好使了
the transmission gives out,
他就開始閃爍其詞  無視保修
he dodges, he ignores the warranty.
我來告訴你們
I'm gonna tell you something,
我們的保修單叫做美國憲法
our warranty is the constitution of the United States,
這張保修單是沒有限制條件的
and there's no limit on that.
他得好好看看憲法
He needs to read the fine print
並且開始回答我們的問題
and start answering our questions.
贓款: 最高涉及到哪一層
如果這裡確有屬實的內容
If any of this is true,
那麼就是國會  白宮
we're talking Congress, the White House,
以及兩黨都算上
both parties...
我是說如果
Now, I'm saying "If,"
但如果這錢看起來像贓款
but when it looks like dirty money,
聞上去也像贓款
and it smells like dirty money,
那肯定有人手上沾著髒東西
somebody has probably got dirt under their nails.
並沒有證據表明洗錢活動確實...
Look, there's no real proof this money laundering is even--
可這其中的聯繫令人擔憂
The connections are troubling,
尤其是安德伍德
especially Underwood.
阿道希資助民主黨期間
He was the House whip the entire time Adohi were
艾拉·薩伊德  《華爾街電訊報》
他一直是黨鞭
contributing to the Democrats,
現在他在總統身邊工作
and he's working side by side with the president now.
總統  這事能一路牽連到白宮嗎
The president. So this goes all the way to the White House?
有可能啊
It might.
這只是假設
It's hypothetical.
而且  你為了證實說法  證據都是挑揀過的
And by the way, you've cherry-picked the facts to make your case.
我沒有什麼說法
I'm not making a case.
我的標題是《政治行動委員會資金引起質疑》
My headline is: PAC Money Raises Questions.
也確實有疑問
And it has.
我並沒有給出答案
I haven't answered those questions,
但我覺得美國人民應該知道答案  你覺得呢
but I think the American people deserve answers. Don't you?
司法部長
You can bet your bottom dollar
百分之百會介入調查
the attorney general is gonna investigate.
這事已經在媒體上引起了軒然大波
With the firestorm this is causing in the media--
我們該怎麼辦
What's our course of action?
作為你的法律顧問  我建議你
As your counsel, I would encourage you
在有更多訊息之前不要和媒體接觸
not to speak to the press until we have more information.
作為普通公民
As your average citizen,
你等的越久  看起來就越可疑
the longer you wait, the more suspicious it looks.
如果有任何的違規行為
If there's been any irregularity,
都與我沒有關係
I had nothing to do with it.
你和塔斯克的友誼
Your friendship with Tusk
會讓你因關連而被認為有罪
implies guilt by association.
那麼我們現在是做有罪推定了嗎
Are we presuming guilt before innocence?
我是個律師
I'm a lawyer,
我不做任何假設
I presume nothing.
但是輿論可沒有法律學位
But public opinion doesn't have a law degree.
讓我們單獨說兩句
Give us a few moments.
我必須建議你  如果我不在場
I have to advise you not to have any conversation
不要和任何人討論這件事
about this matter without me present.
我瞭解你的建議了
Your advisement has been noted.
我就在門口
I'll be right outside.
這就是你一直沒和我說的事嗎
Is this what you were keeping from me?
我們應該遵照你法律顧問的建議  不應該...
We should follow your counsel's advice, and not --
告訴我  錢的事是不是真的
Tell me if it's true, about the money.
比爾不在房間裡  我們可能出現各種...
With Bill out of the room, we open ourselves up to all sort of--
該死  弗蘭克  這事我已經被瞞得太久了
Damn it, Frank! I've been in the dark too long on this.
到此為止了
That ends now.
我不知道任何細節
I don't know any details.
馮說如果大橋的項目通過
Feng told me if the Bridge project got approved,
給共和黨的資金就會斷流
the GOP would stop getting money.
我們批准了項目  資金就停了
We approved it, the money stopped.
老天爺  這樣白宮和錢就有直接聯繫了
Jesus Christ, that connects the White House directly to the money.
不是這樣的
No, sir.
你什麼都不知道  過去是  現在也是
You knew nothing, you still know nothing.
如果司法部發現任何確鑿證據證明外來資金...
If the DOJ finds any concrete evidence of foreign money--
那是雷蒙德·塔斯克的問題
That's Raymond Tusk's head,
不是你的  你什麼都沒做錯
not yours. You've done nothing wrong.
牽連罪  弗蘭克  你也聽到了
Guilt by association, Frank. You heard the man.
如果司法部進行調查  只會證明你是無罪的
If the DOJ investigates, it will only prove your innocence.
沒有人能從這種事情中全身而退
Nobody walks away from something like this without bruises.
但傷不致命
Well, bruises you can survive.
只是不知事到如今要如何避免受牽連
I just don't know how we can avoid it at this point.
如果你想加快程序  平息此事
Unless you want to accelerate the process and get rid of it.
我們可以讓司法部長任命
We could always have the attorney general appoint
一名特別檢察官
a special prosecutor
這主意太糟了
That's a terrible idea.
可能是
Maybe so.
鑑於我們現在的情況  弗蘭克
And given where we are, Frank,
我不是很想接受你的建議
I'm not inclined to follow your suggestions.
我不是說你該這麼做
Well, I wasn't suggesting it as something you should do.
只是提出一種可能
Just as a possibility.
其實  我覺得你不該這麼做
No, in fact, I --I don't think you should.
我覺得這種事拖得越久越好
I think it's better to drag these things out as long as possible.
讓公眾對這個話題產生厭煩
Let the public fatigue on it.
直到中期選舉都一直對我們構成威脅嗎
And have it hanging over our heads until the midterms?
熱度會消退的
It'll lose steam.
如果沒有怎麼辦
What if it doesn't.
國防部提出要對中國南海發起
I've got the Pentagon proposing tactical drone strikes
戰術性無人機襲擊
in the South China Sea.
我不能好幾個月糾纏在這種事裡
I can't be dealing with something like this for months on end.
也許你說得對  是該任命個特別檢察官
Maybe you're right then. A special prosecutor is the way to go.
我沒那麼說  是你說的
I didn't say that, you did.
不  我只是說讓你擺脫這個問題的糾纏
Oh, no. I just meant in terms of getting it off your plate.
如果你及時彙報情況  我就不會有這個問題了
It wouldn't be on my plate if you kept me better informed.
我一直是在幫你撇清干係  先生
I have done nothing but try to insulate you, sir.
剛剛媒體對我的攻擊叫撇清干係嗎
Is that what you call the feeding frenzy I just went through?
我向你鄭重承諾  總統先生
I make this solemn promise to you, Mr. President.
如果走到那一步  我會承擔罪責
I will take the fall if it comes to that,
但不會的
but it won't.
無論你打算如何處理
However you decide to deal with this,
我認為你的直覺是對的
I think your instincts are right.
我們可能不該指派特別檢察官
We probably shouldn't involve a special prosecutor.
讓比爾回來
Send Bill back in.
你知道這事
You knew about this.
塔斯克是我的客戶
Tusk is a client,
-但我不是什麼都知道    -胡說
- doesn't mean I know everything--   - Bullshit.
你之所以能成為格蘭頓-希爾的合夥人
The reason you're a partner at Glendon Hill
就是因為你知道內幕
is because you know the things nobody else does.
你想讓我說什麼
What do you want me to say?
是真的嗎
Is it true?
我們不談公事
We don't talk about work.
我們沒在床上
We're not in bed,
而是在我的辦公室
we're in my fucking office.
在這裡
And in here,
你為弗蘭克賣命
you work for Frank.
我只為我自己賣命
I work for no one but myself.
繼續自欺欺人吧
Keep telling yourself that.
不像你  我不把自己
Unlike you, I don't peddle my goods
賣給出價最高的人
for whoever can pay the highest retainer.
我是很多老大的走狗
I'm the bitch to a lot of top dogs,
我自己很清楚也很情願
I'm fully aware and willing,
但你比我更糟
but you're worse.
你就是弗蘭克的走狗  還拒不相信
You're Frank's bitch and refuse to believe it.
不是這樣
That's not true.
被我戳中了
Case in fucking point.
別轉移話題  你知道這筆錢卻沒有告訴我
Don't turn this. You knew about the money and you didn't tell me.
儘管這事會動搖我的職位
Even though it's thrown my seat into contention.
就算錢的事屬實
Let's say there was money,
我也確實知道
and let's say I did know,
告訴你有什麼好處
what good would it have done?
這說明你不惜看著我輸
It means you were willing to watch me lose!
我只是在尊重你提出的界限
It means I respected the boundaries that you demanded.
-不改變關係  沒有特殊待遇    -這是兩碼事
- No changes, no special treatment.   - This is different!
現在還要開特例了嗎
So now we're making exceptions?
這麼重要的事情當然算特例
When it's this important, yes!
魚和熊掌不可兼得
You can't have it both ways.
你是不是...
Were you...?
我什麼
Was I what?
為了打探弗蘭克的訊息才上我
...fucking me to get info on Frank?
你這麼想嗎
Is that what you think?
我不知道該怎麼想
I don't know what to think.
我對你的關心已經太多了
I care about you more than I should,
但我厭倦了總要一遍遍地說
but I'm getting tired of having to say it.
他被轉移到一家聯邦精神病院做評估
He's being moved to a federal psychiatric facility for assessment.
正式判刑前待在高警戒的拘留中心
then a high-security detention center until the official sentencing.
這是個好訊息
Well, that's good to hear.
壞訊息是  我們希望你近期不要公開活動
The bad news is we don't want you doing any public events for a while.
我的法案馬上要表決了
My bill is about to go to the floor.
我必須公開露面
I need to have a public profile.
你的死亡威脅越來越嚴重
Your death threats continue to rise.
我們冒不起這個險
We can't take the risk.
我都不能離開家了嗎
Am I even allowed to leave the house?
當然可以  但我們希望你避開人群
Of course. But we want you to avoid large crowds.
我們保護你的能力
Our ability to protect--
副總統先生
Mr. Vice President.
出什麼事了
Anything wrong?
我們只是在跟安德伍德夫人彙報
We were just briefing Mrs. Underwood
她的新安保規程
on her new security protocol.
我們待會兒再說行嗎
Can we actually finish this later?
當然可以
Of course.
怎麼樣
How did it go?
他起了疑心
He's skeptical.
要我給特莉莎打電話嗎
Should I call Tricia?
不  不能讓他覺得我在他背後搗鬼
No. It could look like i was trying to go behind his back.
我們只需要靜觀其變
We'll just have to wait and see.
我要說的都說了
I made my case.
希望他不會同意
Hopefully, he'll disagree with it.
但這可能是招錯棋
But this could've been the wrong move.
不要懷疑你自己
Well, don't doubt yourself.
賽斯在過去六小時裡收到了三千餘封電子郵件
Seth has gotten over 3,000 e-mails in the last six hours.
電話被打爆了
The phones are overloaded.
你要完全無視嗎
So you ignore all that?
我不能無視司法部
I can't ignore the Department of Justice.
我能做什麼
What can I do?
等我進監獄了來探視我
Come and visit me when I'm in prison.
你不非得站在門口
You don't have to stand by that door.
放鬆會兒吧
Take a load off.
謝謝  先生  但我應該站著
Thank you, sir, but I'm supposed to stay on my feet.
你不說我也不說
Well, I won't tell if you won't.
要是有人為這個找你麻煩
And if anybody gives you any trouble about this,
或是為任何事找你麻煩
or anything,
他們可以來找我
they can talk to me.
夜晚真美
Beautiful night.
是啊  先生
Yes, sir.
這幾天你不在身邊的感覺真有點怪呢
It's been strange not having you around these last few days.
你要我回到你的安保隊伍中嗎
You want me to switch back to your detail?
不  你跟克萊爾在一起我很欣慰
No, no. I'm glad you're with Claire.
只是你走了我才發覺
I just didn't realize how much
我有多習慣你在我身邊
I got used to your company until you were gone.
在我心中保護她和保護你是一回事
Protecting her is the same as protecting you in my mind.
喝吧
Oh, come on.
你為什麼要做這個
Why do you do this?
做什麼  先生
Do what, sir?
這一直讓我感到敬畏
I've always been awestruck.
竟然會有人願意為別人擋子彈
People who are willing to take a bullet for someone else.
這是我為國家服務的方式
It's how I serve my country.
為國家服務的方式還有很多種
Well, there's a lotta ways to serve your country.
這就是我的方式
And this is my way.
這瓶我還沒喝完呢
Oh, I haven't finished with this one yet.
不是給你的
It's not for you.
我執勤的時候不能喝酒  夫人
I can't drink on duty, ma'am.
也不是給你的
It's not for you either.
好啦  過來一起聊聊
Well, come on over and join the party.
你還沒看膩我的臉嗎
Haven't you got sick of seeing my face yet?
永遠不會  夫人
Never, ma'am.
敬密查姆
To Meechum,
敬他的忠誠與服務
for his loyalty and service.
敬艾德華
To Edward.
我在去我律師辦公室的路上  雷米
I'm on my way to my lawyer's office, Remy.
平常這時候我已經睡了
That's not where I want to be
我並不想去那地方
when I'd usually be in bed.
我無法阻止弗蘭克洩露訊息
I can't stop Frank from leaking things.
是啊  但你可以讓他比我們更遭罪
No, but you can make sure he suffers more than us.
我說"我們"  雷米
And I say "us," Remy,
是因為現在你也是一條繩上的螞蚱了
because your skin is in this game now, too.
你準備否認嗎
Are you gonna deny?
我當然要否認
Of course I'm gonna deny.
這件事每個步驟都是合法的
Every step of this was legal.
他們無法證明其中的聯繫
They can't prove the links between them.
拉尼根那邊呢
What about Lanagin?
他會合作的  我們要擔心的是馮
He'll cooperate. It's Feng we need to worry about.
我想個辦法聯繫他
I'll find a way to get in touch with him.
我們還有一項優勢
We do have one major advantage.
公眾可以恨我
The public can hate me,
但只要克雷頓-維斯特還在盈利
but as long as Clayton West remains profitable,
我的股東們就不會在乎
my stockholders won't care.
弗蘭克可不行
Frank doesn't have the same liberty.
公眾輿論就可以毀了他
Public opinion can demolish him.
你得確保事態會這樣發展
You need to make sure that happens.
我可以跟共和黨人一起想辦法
I can work with the Republicans on that.
我們也會遭人仔細審視
Well, we'll be under the magnifying glass too.
這會變成一場政治迫害
This will be a witch hunt.
那我會讓他們抓到該抓的人
I'll make sure that they pick the right targets.
你要攻擊領導層
What you need to do is go after the leadership.
讓他們受苦
Make them hurt.
他們會為了自救背叛弗蘭克
They'll turn on Frank to save themselves.
博奇  烏麥克  夏普
Birch, Womack, Sharp.
特別是傑姬·夏普
Especially Jackie Sharp.
她是他欽點的人
She's his chosen one.
雷米
Remy?
我聽著呢
I heard you.
我這就行動
I got my marching orders.
就看你的了
I'm counting on you.
一定不辱使命
I'll deliver.
我們明早再談
Let's talk in the morning.
我最看好的兩個人是
The two names I like the most
賈斯汀·蓋因斯和希瑟·鄧巴
are Justin Gaines and Heather Dunbar.
蓋因斯的資歷更高
Gaines has better credentials.
但他跟政府關係太近
But he's close to the administration.
如果不是共和黨阻撓
I would've made him a federal judge
我已經讓他當上聯邦法官了
if the GOP hadn't blocked it.
這一點很重要
That's an important point.
鄧巴很勇敢  她絕對可以勝任
Dunbar's got grit. She's more than qualified.
而且沒有負擔
And there's no baggage there.
但她更難以捉摸
But she's more unpredictable.
如果司法部長認為她是個未知數
Well, I doubt the attorney general would have put her on his list
也不會把她提上名單了
if he thought she was a wild card.
先生  我必須說
Sir, I have to say,
我認為這一步時機不到
I think this step is premature.
我們該緩緩  看看司法部自己採取什麼行動
We should hold off and see what the DOJ does on its own.
我不想這麼做  比爾
I don't want to do it, Bill
但我的擔心是
But my fear is this.
如果我們等著水從熱升至沸騰
If we wait until the water goes from hot to boiling,
會顯得我們太保守了  缺乏積極性
we seem reactionary, not proactive.
但積極也可能顯得防禦性太強
But proactive could also seem defensive.
就像嫌疑人在別人問之前就大喊
Like the suspect that screams "I didn't do it"
不是我幹的
before anyone asks.
除此之外  我們根本沒時間做準備
Aside from that, we simply haven't had time to prepare.
也許等幾禮拜
Maybe wait a couple of weeks.
那就達不到目的了
That defeats the purpose.
那就等幾天
Then a few days.
我要選鄧巴
I'd like to go with Dunbar.
-先生    -我決定了
- Sir--   - I've made my decision.
比爾  請你將我的意思轉達給司法部長
Bill, I'd like you to convey my wishes to the attorney general.
最終還是得由他決定
Ultimately, the decision is his.
我們不能給他施加壓力
We can't appear to be pressuring him.
當然了
Of course not.
謝謝  先生
Thank you, sir.
唯一比說服別人按我的意願做事
The only thing more satisfying than
更讓我感到滿足的
convincing someone to do what I want,
就是故意沒能說服他們
is failing to persuade them on purpose.
就像"禁止進入"標誌
It's like a "Do Not Enter" Sign,
簡直就是在求你走進去
it just begs you to walk through the door.
道爾對我們的初步背景調查已經進行過半了
Doyle's about halfway through our initial background check.
每位捐贈人
Every donor,
每次政治活動
every political event.
鄧巴可能調查的每件事
Everything that Dunbar might be looking into.
很好  賽斯呢
Good. Seth?
我們要避免做任何正式聲明
We avoid any official statement,
聽總統的指令
follow the president's cue.
同時  我想打幾個非正式電話
In the meantime, I'd like to make some off the record calls.
透露說你樂於接受調查
You welcome the investigation,
這樣做是對的  等等
it's the right step, et cetera.
讓民眾瞭解你的個人看法
Give folks the personal touch.
沒問題  只要不顯得我們防禦性太強
That's fine, as long as we don't come off defensive.
讓我看看你要給誰打電話
I'd like to see a list of who you'd be calling.
有些人可能會很忙
Some of this is gonna be on the fly,
如果能讓我自由發揮會更好
it'd be great if I had a little leeway.
讓賽斯幹他的  道爾的事就夠你忙的了
Let Seth do his thing, you'll have your hands full with Doyle.
我事後告訴你我都打給誰了
I'll let you know who I've called.
好  工作去吧
All right, let's get to work.
先生
Sir?
什麼事
Yes, what is it?
我知道你要委派任務
I understand that you need to delegate,
但你當著賽斯的面反駁我
but when you contradict me in front of Seth,
會削弱我對他的控制
it compromises my authority over him.
你不能事事管著他  我們要忙的事很多
You can't micromanage, we have too much to do.
賽斯還是我們團隊裡的新人
Seth is still new to the team.
我要確保他在好好完成任務
I need to make sure that he's doing his job properly.
我覺得他在好好做
Well, I think he is.
我是你的故障保險  先生
I am your failsafe, sir.
但如果你不讓我這麼做  我就沒辦法了
But I can't be that if you won't let me.
是嗎  道格  你是我的故障保險嗎
Are you, Doug? My failsafe?
你還懷疑這點嗎
Do you doubt that?
我們正在全速飛向一場颶風
We're flying full throttle into a hurricane,
你卻在談辦公室政治
and you're talking office politics
而不是集中全力確保我們不會被搞垮
instead of focusing on making sure we don't get ripped apart.
你說得對  先生  我不該提這事
You're right, sir. I shouldn't have brought it up.
她還在那裡嗎
Is she still there?
在  我告訴她我去散個步
Yeah. I told her I was going for a walk.
道格  我知道你說過你想讓她走
Look, Doug, I know you said you wanted her gone,
但你要理解  我只求...
but you have to understand that all I'm asking is --
她可以留下來
She can stay.
什麼
What?
她不一定得走  她可以留下來
She doesn't have to leave. She can stay.
我相信你知道分寸
I trust you to be smart.
你能讀書給我聽嗎
Will you read to me?
我的《聖經》在屋裡
My bible is inside.
不非得是《聖經》
Doesn't have to be the bible.
隨便找點你手機上的
Just pull up something on your phone.
比如什麼
Like what?
《雙城記》  我媽媽以前會念給我聽
Tale of Two Cities. My mom used to read it to me.
那是最美好的時代
It was the best of times,
那是最糟糕的時代
it was the worst of times,
那是智慧的年頭
it was the age of wisdom,
那是愚昧的年頭
it was the age of foolishness,
那是信仰的紀元
it was the epoch of belief,
那是懷疑的紀元
it was the epoch of incredulity,
那是光明的季節
it was the season of Light,
那是黑暗的季節
it was the season of Darkness,
那是希望的春天
it was the spring of hope,
那是絕望的冬天
the winter of despair,
我們擁有一切
we had everything before us,
我們一無所有
we had nothing before us,
我們都將直奔天堂
we were all going direct to Heaven,
我們都將直落地獄
we were all going direct the other way."
你好
Hello?
道格  是你嗎
Doug, is that you?
喂
Hello?
道格
Doug?
喬帕  道·斯坦普
是的  道格  就是你
Yes, Doug, it is you.
■
本集一開始  一個反墮胎者試圖襲擊克萊爾
美國建國早期
除了一些法律禁止銷售能夠引起晚期流產的藥物之外
墮胎行為是被允許的
自從1821年康涅狄格州第一個通過了禁止墮胎的法律後
其它各州也紛紛仿效
聯邦政府也在1883年通過了禁止傳播避孕和墮胎工具
藥物和資訊的"康斯托克法"
在1973年1月22日最高法院公佈"羅訴韋德案"判決結果之前
除非妊娠威脅到孕婦的生命安全  墮胎在美國全境都是非法的
■
1973年  美國最高法院9名大法官
以7比2判定德克薩斯州的墮胎禁令違憲
判決書指出  個人隱私是受到憲法保護的
而在這種保護之下  女性有自主選擇是否終止妊娠的權利
這便是美國司法歷史上著名的"羅訴韋德案"
這個判決並沒有給關於墮胎的爭論畫上句號
在過去41年中  圍繞著這一判決的鬥爭從未停止過
包括墮胎權和生育權在內的女性權益問題
不僅引起了美國社會的廣泛關注和討論
還在美國的黨派政治鬥爭和總統選舉中扮演了重要的角色
■
在美國的政治光譜中  左翼民主黨多是支援墮胎的"選擇派"
而共和黨所代表的右翼保守力量多是反對墮胎的"生命派"
每年在"羅訴韋德案"宣判的紀念日
都會有"生命派"活動人士在華盛頓進行名為"生命進軍"的大規模集會
2007年  美國最高法院判定
小布什政府的"晚期墮胎禁令"沒有違反憲法
民意調查顯示  目前在美國
大多數人(52%)反對不加限制的無條件墮胎
只有26%的人認為在任何情況下都可以墮胎
有20%認為任何情況下都不可以墮胎